Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sujit-kange-5ba09043 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Telecommunications
GSM
CDMA

Languages

Hindi (Full Professional)

Marathi (Full Professional)

Kannada (Limited Working)

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Maharashtra State Certificate In Information Technology (MS-CIT)

Certified Optical Fiber Network Planning & Project Management Professional

Project Management Professional (PMP)

Sujit Kange

Electrical Engineer at Synergy Telecommunications
Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Extensive experience in the field of telecom project, O&M of passive infra including energy management, site management, fault reduction, installation, commissioning of DG set, SMPS power plant, PIU, TPS, Ac, Battery Bank, Voltage stabilizer, UPS, alarm multiplexer, earth pit etc. In-depth understanding of the deployment, execution, implementation, vendor mamagement, RFI, site upgradation, site survey, NOC from local authoroties, , electrical connection. Know-how about telecom GBT, RTT, Pole, DG, shelter, I/D & O/D BTS foundation & erection. Also i have 1 year & 10 months experience in continuous mass production engineering industry.

Experience

Synergy Teleccommunications Pvt. Ltd. Electrical Engineer September 2009 - Present (14 years) Anywhere In Maharashtra

Installation,commissioning & testing of DG set, PIU,TPS,SMPS Power Plant,Battery Bank,UPS,AC,Voltage Stabilizer & Alarm Multiplexer etc. Pipe & Plate earthing, GSM,RF,Microwave work.

Reliance Communications Ltd. (Through: Utility Powertech Ltd.) Electrical Engineer August 2008 - June 2009 (11 months)

Pune Area, India

netallation commissioning & testing of DG set Battery

Installation,commissioning & testing of DG set, Battery Bank, SMPS Power Plant, AC, Plate & Pipe earthing.

Indian Telephone Industries Ltd. Sr. Technician August 2005 - July 2008 (3 years) Solapur Area, India Installation, commissioning & testing of DG Set,SMPS Power Plant,Battery Bank, AC, BTS, BSC, RF & Antenna work etc.

Kalyani Lemmerz Ltd.

Trainee

September 2004 - July 2005 (11 months)

Pune Area, India

Preventive maintenance on power press machines, crane control circuit, ACB & OCB breakers, induction motors, crane panel maintenance, Kaizen, Six Sigma knowledge & implementation.

Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd.
Electrical Apprentice
September 2003 - August 2004 (1 year)
Solapur Area, India

Controlled induction furnace melting programme through electrical panel.

Preventive maintenance of induction furnace, EOT crane control circuit, DM plant & cupola. Process control instruments (Measuring Flow, Temperature, Pressure & Level Transmitter)

Education

Government Polytechnic, Solapur

Diploma In Electrical, Electrical Engineering Technologies · (1999 - 2003)

Pune Board SSC · (1998 - 1999)